<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
	<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
		<MASTER_PAD_VERSION>3.11</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
		<MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>PADGen 3.1.1.50 http://www.padgen.org</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
		<MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://pad.asp-software.org</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
	</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
	<Company_Info>
		<Company_Name>Conderella</Company_Name>
		<Address_1>ElShorta ElAskarya</Address_1>
		<Address_2 />
		<City_Town>Bani Suef</City_Town>
		<State_Province>Bani Suef</State_Province>
		<Zip_Postal_Code>62111</Zip_Postal_Code>
		<Country>Egypt</Country>
		<Company_WebSite_URL>http://www.conderella.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
		<Contact_Info>
			<Author_First_Name>Ahmed</Author_First_Name>
			<Author_Last_Name>Saad</Author_Last_Name>
			<Author_Email>mail@conderella.com</Author_Email>
			<Contact_First_Name>Ahmed</Contact_First_Name>
			<Contact_Last_Name>Saad</Contact_Last_Name>
			<Contact_Email>mail@conderella.com</Contact_Email>
		</Contact_Info>
		<Support_Info>
			<Sales_Email>customers@conderella.com</Sales_Email>
			<Support_Email>support@conderella.com</Support_Email>
			<General_Email>mail@conderella.com</General_Email>
			<Sales_Phone>+2 (011) 58 735 718</Sales_Phone>
			<Support_Phone>+2 (011) 58 735 718</Support_Phone>
			<General_Phone>+2 (011) 58 735 718</General_Phone>
			<Fax_Phone />
		</Support_Info>
	</Company_Info>
	<Program_Info>
		<Program_Name>Cacadu</Program_Name>
		<Program_Version>1.0.12927.1</Program_Version>
		<Program_Release_Month>10</Program_Release_Month>
		<Program_Release_Day>04</Program_Release_Day>
		<Program_Release_Year>2012</Program_Release_Year>
		<Program_Cost_Dollars>49.99</Program_Cost_Dollars>
		<Program_Cost_Other_Code />
		<Program_Cost_Other />
		<Program_Type>Shareware</Program_Type>
		<Program_Release_Status>Minor Update</Program_Release_Status>
		<Program_Install_Support>Install and Uninstall</Program_Install_Support>
		<Program_OS_Support>Win2000,Win7 x32,Win7 x64,Win98,WinOther,WinServer,WinVista,WinVista x64,WinXP,Other</Program_OS_Support>
		<Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
		<Program_Change_Info>Bug fixes and minor changes.</Program_Change_Info>
		<Program_Specific_Category>Utilities</Program_Specific_Category>
		<Program_Category_Class>System Utilities::Automation Tools</Program_Category_Class>
		<Program_System_Requirements>.Net Framework version: 4.0 or higher</Program_System_Requirements>
		<File_Info>
			<File_Size_Bytes>14435048</File_Size_Bytes>
			<File_Size_K>14096</File_Size_K>
			<File_Size_MB>13.77</File_Size_MB>
		</File_Info>
		<Expire_Info>
			<Has_Expire_Info>Y</Has_Expire_Info>
			<Expire_Count>15</Expire_Count>
			<Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
			<Expire_Other_Info>15-Day Trial</Expire_Other_Info>
			<Expire_Month />
			<Expire_Day />
			<Expire_Year />
		</Expire_Info>
	</Program_Info>
	<Program_Descriptions>
		<English>
			<Keywords>windows automation, task scheduler, job scheduler, automate repetitive tasks, automation software, windows scheduler, automation tools, scheduling software, scheduled tasks, windows 7 task scheduler, job scheduling software</Keywords>
			<Char_Desc_45>Customizable Windows Automation Software</Char_Desc_45>
			<Char_Desc_80>Customizable Windows Task Scheduling &amp; Automation Made Easy</Char_Desc_80>
			<Char_Desc_250>Cacadu is a Windows application that allows automation of Windows tasks by letting the users define Tasks, Actions and Triggers.</Char_Desc_250>
			<Char_Desc_450>Every computer user knows there are programs they need to run every time they log into the computer or tasks which need run periodically. Cacadu is the application for you. With Cacadu's simple &amp; customizable user interface you can easily automate the tasks that will make your computer experience more gratifying. Configure applications to start with every login, or run on a periodic basis and do so with more flexibility than Windows offers.</Char_Desc_450>
			<Char_Desc_2000>Creating, editing, and managing your Windows Automation tasks has never been simpler customizable, and powerful that with Conderella's Cacadu Windows Task Scheduler. Running on top of the .NET 4.x framework, this application provides a simple user interface that allows for quick creation of automated tasks to suit your needs.  
 
Get your desktop set up just right by launching all your word processor, browser, and key applications upon logging in. Are you an IT professional or systems administrator? Need more power? Cacadu can do more - much more. Cacadu is fully capable of sourcing in either local or global variables which can be used to control the flow of actions with a single task or all tasks. Cacadu allows you to edit the task properties for additional customization. Graphically &amp; edit view the associated actions for a task and group the tasks for better task management. Define responses to errors for alerts, number of retries, ignore &amp; continue, or quit. Cacadu logs task execution history and errors for troubleshooting purposes. Cacadu gives the user the ability to build truly modular and customized tasks to meet their needs.  
 
So whether you are looking to automate the upload of data files offsite, launch &amp; auto-configure a virtual machine, extend or wrap additional functionality into freeware utilities that have no built-in task scheduling, Cacadu will prove itself scalable. After the 14-day trial and purchase, you will have a 30-day money back guarantee followed by one year of free product updates and technical support. Additionally, the application itself is well documented and online chat is available for support along with the ability to open support tickets. With all the added value provided in the purchase of this Windows Automation application, your needs will be satisfied. Download the application now and extend the power of your computer.</Char_Desc_2000>
		</English>
	</Program_Descriptions>
	<Web_Info>
		<Application_URLs>
			<Application_Info_URL>http://cacadu.conderella.com</Application_Info_URL>
			<Application_Order_URL>http://cacadu.conderella.com/order/</Application_Order_URL>
			<Application_Screenshot_URL>http://cacadu.conderella.com/wp-content/gallery/general/cacadu-main-window_800-600.png</Application_Screenshot_URL>
			<Application_Icon_URL>http://cacadu.conderella.com/wp-content/gallery/general/cacadu_icon.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
			<Application_XML_File_URL>http://cacadu.conderella.com/docs/cacadu_pad.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
		</Application_URLs>
		<Download_URLs>
			<Primary_Download_URL>http://conderella.com/downloads/Cacadu.exe</Primary_Download_URL>
			<Secondary_Download_URL>http://dl.dropbox.com/u/5721699/cacadu-appcast/Cacadu.exe</Secondary_Download_URL>
			<Additional_Download_URL_1 />
			<Additional_Download_URL_2 />
		</Download_URLs>
	</Web_Info>
	<Permissions>
		<Distribution_Permissions>See End User License Agreement.</Distribution_Permissions>
		<EULA>END-USER LICENSE AGREEMENT FOR Cacadu IMPORTANT PLEASE READ THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS LICENSE AGREEMENT CAREFULLY BEFORE CONTINUING WITH THIS PROGRAM INSTALL: Conderella Soft End-User License Agreement ("EULA") is a legal agreement between you (either an individual or a single entity) and Conderella Soft. for the Conderella Soft product(s) identified above which may include associated software components, media, printed materials, and "online" or electronic documentation ("SOFTWARE PRODUCT"). By installing, copying, or otherwise using the SOFTWARE PRODUCT, you agree to be bound by the terms of this EULA. This license agreement represents the entire agreement concerning the program between you and Conderella Soft, (referred to as "licenser"), and it supersedes any prior proposal, representation, or understanding between the parties. If you do not agree to the terms of this EULA, do not install or use the SOFTWARE PRODUCT. 
The SOFTWARE PRODUCT is protected by copyright laws and international copyright treaties, as well as other intellectual property laws and treaties. The SOFTWARE PRODUCT is licensed, not sold. 
1. GRANT OF LICENSE. 
The SOFTWARE PRODUCT is licensed as follows: 
(a) Installation and Use.
Conderella Soft grants you the right to install and use copies of the SOFTWARE PRODUCT on your computer running a validly licensed copy of the operating system for which the SOFTWARE PRODUCT was designed [e.g., Windows 95, Windows NT, Windows 98, Windows 2000 , Windows 2003, Windows XP, Windows ME, Windows Vista, Windows 7, Windows 8].
(b) Backup Copies.
You may also make copies of the SOFTWARE PRODUCT as may be necessary for backup and archival purposes.
2. DESCRIPTION OF OTHER RIGHTS AND LIMITATIONS.
(a) Maintenance of Copyright Notices.
You must not remove or alter any copyright notices on any and all copies of the SOFTWARE PRODUCT.
(b) Distribution.
You may not distribute registered copies of the SOFTWARE PRODUCT to third parties. Evaluation versions available for download from Conderella Soft website may be freely distributed.
(c) Prohibition on Reverse Engineering, Decompilation, and Disassembly.
You may not reverse engineer, decompile, or disassemble the SOFTWARE PRODUCT, except and only to the extent that such activity is expressly permitted by applicable law notwithstanding this limitation. 
(d) Rental.
You may not rent, lease, or lend the SOFTWARE PRODUCT.
(e) Support Services.
Conderella Soft may provide you with support services related to the SOFTWARE PRODUCT ("Support Services"). Any supplemental software code provided to you as part of the Support Services shall be considered part of the SOFTWARE PRODUCT and subject to the terms and conditions of this EULA. 
(f) Compliance with Applicable Laws.
You must comply with all applicable laws regarding use of the SOFTWARE PRODUCT.
3. TERMINATION 
Without prejudice to any other rights, Conderella Soft may terminate this EULA if you fail to comply with the terms and conditions of this EULA. In such event, you must destroy all copies of the SOFTWARE PRODUCT in your possession.
4. COPYRIGHT
All title, including but not limited to copyrights, in and to the SOFTWARE PRODUCT and any copies thereof are owned by Conderella Soft or its suppliers. All title and intellectual property rights in and to the content which may be accessed through use of the SOFTWARE PRODUCT is the property of the respective content owner and may be protected by applicable copyright or other intellectual property laws and treaties. This EULA grants you no rights to use such content. All rights not expressly granted are reserved by Conderella Soft. 
5. NO WARRANTIES 
Conderella Soft expressly disclaims any warranty for the SOFTWARE PRODUCT. The SOFTWARE PRODUCT is provided As Is without any express or implied warranty of any kind, including but not limited to any warranties of merchantability, noninfringement, or fitness of a particular purpose. Conderella Soft does not warrant or assume responsibility for the accuracy or completeness of any information, text, graphics, links or other items contained within the SOFTWARE PRODUCT. Conderella Soft makes no warranties respecting any harm that may be caused by the transmission of a computer virus, worm, time bomb, logic bomb, or other such computer program. Conderella Soft further expressly disclaims any warranty or representation to Authorized Users or to any third party.
6. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
In no event shall Conderella Soft be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, lost profits, business interruption, or lost information) rising out of Authorized Users' use of or inability to use the SOFTWARE PRODUCT, even if Conderella Soft has been advised of the possibility of such damages. In no event will Conderella Soft be liable for loss of data or for indirect, special, incidental, consequential (including lost profit), or other damages based in contract, tort or otherwise. Conderella Soft shall have no liability with respect to the content of the SOFTWARE PRODUCT or any part thereof, including but not limited to errors or omissions contained therein, libel, infringements of rights of publicity, privacy, trademark rights, business interruption, personal injury, loss of privacy, moral rights or the disclosure of confidential information. </EULA>
	</Permissions>
	<Affiliates>
		<Affiliates_FORM>Y</Affiliates_FORM>
		<Affiliates_VERSION>1.4</Affiliates_VERSION>
		<Affiliates_URL>http://pad.asp-software.org/extensions/Affiliates.htm</Affiliates_URL>
		<Affiliates_Information_Page>http://cacadu.conderella.com/affiliate-program</Affiliates_Information_Page>
		<Affiliates_Avangate_Order_Page>http://content.avangate.com/check_affiliate/?account=ltvKnpXcgH4=&amp;avgurl=https%3A//secure.avangate.com/order/checkout.php%3FPRODS%3D4570835%26QTY%3D1%26CART%3D1%26CARD%3D1=&amp;otherurl=https%3A//secure.avangate.com/order/checkout.php%3FPRODS%3D4570835%26QTY%3D1%26CART%3D1%26CARD%3D1</Affiliates_Avangate_Order_Page>
		<Affiliates_Avangate_Vendor_ID>CONDRELL</Affiliates_Avangate_Vendor_ID>
		<Affiliates_Avangate_Product_ID>4570835</Affiliates_Avangate_Product_ID>
		<Affiliates_Avangate_Maximum_Commission_Rate>30%</Affiliates_Avangate_Maximum_Commission_Rate>
		<Affiliates_BMTMicro_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_BMTMicro_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_BMTMicro_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_BMTMicro_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_Cleverbridge_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_Cleverbridge_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_Cleverbridge_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_Cleverbridge_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_clixGalore_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_clixGalore_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_clixGalore_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_clixGalore_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_CommissionJunction_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_CommissionJunction_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_CommissionJunction_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_CommissionJunction_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_DigiBuy_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_DigiBuy_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_DigiBuy_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_DigiBuy_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_DigitalCandle_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_DigitalCandle_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_DigitalCandle_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_DigitalCandle_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_Emetrix_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_Emetrix_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_Emetrix_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_Emetrix_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_eSellerate_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_eSellerate_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_eSellerate_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_eSellerate_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_iPortis_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_iPortis_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_iPortis_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_iPortis_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_Kagi_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_Kagi_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_Kagi_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_Kagi_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_LinkShare_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_LinkShare_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_LinkShare_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_LinkShare_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_NorthStarSol_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_NorthStarSol_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_NorthStarSol_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_NorthStarSol_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_OneNetworkDirect_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_OneNetworkDirect_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_OneNetworkDirect_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_OneNetworkDirect_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_Order1_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_Order1_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_Order1_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_Order1_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_Osolis_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_Osolis_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_Osolis_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_Osolis_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_Plimus_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_Plimus_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_Plimus_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_Plimus_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_Regnet_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_Regnet_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_Regnet_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_Regnet_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_Regnow_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_Regnow_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_Regnow_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_Regnow_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_Regsoft_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_Regsoft_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_Regsoft_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_Regsoft_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_ShareIt_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_ShareIt_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_ShareIt_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_ShareIt_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_Shareasale_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_Shareasale_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_Shareasale_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_Shareasale_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_SWReg_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_SWReg_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_SWReg_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_SWReg_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_V-Share_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_V-Share_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_V-Share_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_V-Share_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_VFree_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_VFree_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_VFree_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_VFree_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
		<Affiliates_Yaskifo_Order_Page />
		<Affiliates_Yaskifo_Vendor_ID />
		<Affiliates_Yaskifo_Product_ID />
		<Affiliates_Yaskifo_Maximum_Commission_Rate />
	</Affiliates>
	<ASP>
		<ASP_FORM>Y</ASP_FORM>
		<ASP_Member>N</ASP_Member>
		<ASP_Member_Number />
	</ASP>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
